<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://spknash.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://spknash.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2023-07-17T13:43:47+00:00</updated><id>https://spknash.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">First Post!</title><link href="https://spknash.github.io/blog/2023/first-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Post!" /><published>2023-07-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://spknash.github.io/blog/2023/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://spknash.github.io/blog/2023/first-post/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="motivation">Motivation</h2>

<p>Hello there! this is my first post. My motivation for writing here is to document my learning in the topics I am interested in (ML/DL, system design, math, programming, tech, etc.). I have always been very interested in how individuals continue to learn and improve their craft. I’ve watched countless interviews from Kobe Bryant, MJ, and other athletes talking about their preparation. I’ve read about Malcolm Gladwell’s 10,000-hour rule which states: Mastery in a skill is simply a matter of practicing for 10,000 hours. Within the realm of technology, I thought Jeremy Howards thoughts on how to learn are very insightful. He believes that practical application of a new concept is a more valuable first step than trying to understand all the foundational underpinnings. After taking his course Practical Deep Learning and reflecting on my own experiences through the years I tend to agree with that sentiment. Despite having so much information about how to learn, and how to improve I feel like there are still so many questions that are left unanswered. I want even more details: If you’re trying to learn more about Deep learning, what did you do each week? How did your view/understanding of a topic change as you went deeper into it? I am interested in these types of questions and by documenting my learning and improvement starting from the level of a beginner in many ways, I will leave behind a record of what I did, and how it helped me learn. This record will be really interesting for me to look back on, and hopefully it can help someone else too.</p>

<hr />]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="intro" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of things I will talk about here]]></summary></entry></feed>